chineselaundry.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Chinese Laundry

**UPDATED JANUARY 23, 2017**

**CHINESE LAUNDRY PRIVACY POLICY**

Chinese Laundry Lifestyle, LLC (hereinafter referred to as “Chinese Laundry”, “we” or “us”) operates the website located at [ **www.ChineseLaundry.com**](http://www.chineselaundry.com/) (the ”Website”) and the stores located in the United States. We recognize that you care about how information about you is collected, used and shared so we have created this Privacy Policy to inform you about the collection, use and sharing practices.

**PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY AND IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS, PLEASE FEEL FREE TO CONTACT US.   BY VISITING THE WEBSITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AS OUTLINED IN THE PRIVACY POLICY. **

**WHEN DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION?**

We may collect information about you anytime you interact with us such as when you (i) access or browse the Website, (ii) order products or services through the Website, (iii) communicate with us either by e-mail, over the telephone or in any other manner, (iv) elect to participate in any of our product promotions, (v) request information about products and services and (vii) visit any of our stores and provide us with information at the store.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

The information we collect from you or about you may vary depending on how you use the Website, your visit(s) to the stores and information you may choose to provide to us and to other sources.  The information we collect is generally of two types – personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information comprises any information that can help us identify or locate an individual, including, without limitation, an individual’s name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card number. Non-personally identifiable information comprises information that does not by itself identify an individual.  This information generally includes anonymous information about an individual’s use of the Website that includes, among other things, information concerning date and time of visit, the pages of the Website visited, path through the Website, IP address, the type of browser and operating system used.

**WHAT DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve the Website (we strive to continually improve the Website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions
  * To send periodic emails -- the email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order; if you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Except as required by law, your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet cannot be completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee our security measures. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures.

When using the Website, you should ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account information by limiting access to your computer (or other device) and browser by signing off after you havefinished accessing your account.

**DO WE USE COOKIES?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow it to) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly.

**DO WE DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating the Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**THIRD PARTY LINKS**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on the Website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites and encourage you to read and fully understand their privacy policies. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of the Website and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**

If you are a California resident, you may request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write us at the address below.

**CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT COMPLIANCE**

In compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not intentionally collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. If you are under the age of thirteen (13), you should not register, order, purchase or provide information to or from us and you should use this Website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. If you have knowledge that a child under the age of thirteen (13) has submitted personal information to us, please email us [ **cs@chineselaundry.com**](mailto:cs@chineselaundry.com) and we will remove that child’s personal information from our files.

**INTERNATIONAL USERS**

Our digital operations are conducted, in whole or in part, in the United States. Regardless of where you live, you consent to have your personal data transferred, processed and stored in the United States and allow us to collect and use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

Please also visit our [ **Terms and Conditions**](https://www.chineselaundry.com/terms.html) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of the Website.

**INTEGRITY**

During the account sign-in process you can review, change or remove the information you have submitted.  We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible and encourage you to promptly update your information if it changes.  You may, at any time, access your information to update, modify or delete any inaccuracies by accessing your account through the Web Site.  You may also request us to remove your account information from our databases and we will try to remove as much information as possible.  However, as we generally keep information related to past transactions for our records, we will not be able to completely remove your information.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We may change our policy at any time by posting a new version of it on the Website without notice.  We encourage you to check the Website regularly for information about revisions to this Privacy Policy.  In the event that we change our Privacy Policy, such changes will affect all of the information we collect after any such change.  If you object to the change to our Privacy Policy, then you must contact us in writing regarding your objection. Your continued use of the Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes.

**CONTACTING US**

We welcome your questions, comments and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy or any other issue at [**cs@chineselaundry.com**](mailto:cs@chineselaundry.com) or write us at:

Chinese Laundry  
Attn: Legal  
3485 S. La Cienega Boulevard  
Los Angeles, CA  90016
